<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Experience Living ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Experience Living ]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 03:20:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do you ever ask yourself.....Is this really living life? ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4a3b431f-0634-4953-83bf-18d591ef2af5.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/do-you-ever-ask-yourselfim-i-really-living-my-life/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">10b2b939-8778-4265-a6df-c9fc81b5e2fc</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 03:43:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Tiny House Foundation! ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>My Tiny House Foundation! </h1><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/75234755-40d0-47ca-a22e-38f520741957.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/my-tiny-house-foundation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a206b66-8e42-4675-a7b2-771893f6d0cd</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 03:20:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MY NEW BEGINNING!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/75836d87-b0ed-4385-86a0-fc4620b4e843.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/my-new-beginning/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">240661ff-058d-4632-b34b-744c52c6a26a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 05:40:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c0a50956-98ec-4e25-831a-08000842dc5a.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/at-age-40-this-picture-has-come-to-mean-so-much-to-me-i-a/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6c2cc26d-ca41-45c7-a424-fd228951d82a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 05:48:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/94f1c588-2258-4d64-9eed-97dd5984abfc.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/as-i-sit-here-in-the-extreme-quiet-of-this-lonely-house-fi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4be9ae78-5ede-4d65-936e-f42a062638ca</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 23:55:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[0329160019.jpg]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>0329160019.jpg</h1><p>It's so very odd to me that I cannot remember basic things, and so many people come up to me and talk to me like they have known me their whole life and I have no idea who they are. It truly brakes me every time. Yet I can look at a photo and it's like I'm there, and can recall every moment. I was 22 in this picture, having the time of my life! I was very much involved with the outrages club scene. [AKA MIND-A-LATER] The only thing on my agenda for every night and day was to outdo the crazy fun time I had the day before! On this day I was at my mother's house very nervous because I had made a real commitment to someone, and that someone was a girl. Sure, I had messed around with girls, yet no one knew, at least not my friends that I had been going to school with since the first grade, and not my parents. I even brought my new girlfriend along to meet my mom, and then I had her leave before I told her. I remember skimming that pool that day for two hours straight, it was already clean. I was so nervous, my hands were dripping. I'm sitting on the diving board of the pool, when I finally built up the courage my mother was on the other side of the pool in a lounge chair laying in the sun, with her sunglasses on. I said,"Mom you know the girl that was here?" She said,"Yes". Me, "Well, she is my girlfriend". As I took a big gulp in my throat feeling like I was going to meet some sort of end of I don't know what. She said,"I know." I said,"No mom like we are dating kind of girlfriend."She said,"Mindy I know that, I have known that since you were six years old, I'm your mother."Well, at that moment I didn't know if I should be happy, or if I should have walked over and wring her neck! I said,"MOM! If you knew this whole f#*#@*g time, why in the hell did you not share it with me!!!" All I could think of is all the years of shame, pain, and I had no one to talk to. She said,"I knew you would tell me when you were ready." Well My mother and I then had years of very hard life to work out, and I was already angry at her for a world of shit I had no way of sorting through at that time, so unfortunately for her that was one more thing for me to add to the very high mountain of Mindy's your not right list for her mother. Looking back I see things MUCH differently about that day, My mother was the one that loved me for who I was, and being gay meant NOTHING to her. She got over that when I wouldn't play with dolls, yet fell in love with my dirt bike at age six. So that's the beginning of my coming out story, I spoke of this because it reminded me of something that an ongoing situation with a once best friend flared up again yesterday. It was going to happen, I just hoped with all that I am It would not have. I'm hoping by the end of this after three years of being totally heartbroken over it, I can find peace and a pocket to put it in. So back to when I was 22, okay mom knows one down only the rest of Orlando to go....I have lived with my roommate and best friend for the past three years, I truly love her, and we have the BEST of times together [I wish more than anything that I could find you] she is a Jersey girl, yet I did not think she would have taken it the way she did. At first she was mad and shocked,"You're not gay you get the hottest guys falling all over you every night, and they keep coming BACK she screamed! Your THE-MIND-A-LATER the PIMP are you f#####g crazy!!!"Then she say's,"Mindy this chic better be hot, if you bring home a bull dike I will kill you!" I wanted to laugh so hard, yet I couldn't because she was dead serious. Not about the killing part, but I think in her mind the only way she could be okay with it is if I somehow kept a part of who I was, meaning if I had arm candy, and it was a girl well in Orlando at that time I could still maintain my social status and get what I want. I was 10 steps ahead, no way was I coming out of the closet and publicly displaying a commitment to a girl, without her being a total 10. No Worries there, now healthy that was not considered and I was too young and dumb to know any better. This was my first real relationship would be doomed no matter what. Nevertheless, my good buddy got through it, it took her a bit of adjustment, but in the end she loved me just the same, and we remained very close for years, until we lose touch. Now is what really took me back was the ones I didn't even see it coming, it just side swiped me, and my back was on the floor. Take my friend that I had through out school. Wow, we did some amazing things together, like renting a convertible white, red top Mustang and went from Orlando to the Giants stadium in N.Y. City, back down to South Beach Miami baby!!! Why you ask.... To follow Metallica with G & R opening up for them, yes, it was amazing, saw them 8 times in a week if I remember correctly! Also ate some spaghetti with Jason one night backstage. Little BIG moments!!! So we had major history, roommates, she even flew to N.Y. My senior year to visit me for a week. I think telling her no big deal. Call her, tell her, and she said,"you're disgusting, I can't believe you do that!" we never spoke again. There were a few like that, fear of what you don't understand, I think, or maybe fear of something they saw in them self's. I don't think I will ever really know, yet I will never forget the hurt, and feeling of being tossed out like garbage like I had felt so many times as a child............ THAT"S IT!!!!! What an ah ha moment, that's when the deep seed of feeling jaded by people was planted, I mean the seed I carried with me from childhood all the time, but that's when I planted it!!!! When I invested in people, I did that like I do everything else....I gave everything! This is a TRIP, because I forgot this. I could not understand how people that were so bonded with me, could just turn like that, as if they had just meet me a week ago, and we were sitting in Mrs. Adams 4th grade class together, that's how far back we went! How those peaces just would not fit together for me. That's when I took a long hard look around, and said to myself,"If the people you grow with, are willing to turn on you like that, no one can ever be fully trusted, sooner or much later they will disappoint, or seek to hurt you." This is pretty heavy.....To Be Continued...Okay I've had some time to chew on that, I'm still floored yet I think I'm able to find some words now. So I'm a pretty jaded person when it comes to people, I almost always see everyone with a raised eyebrow until proven different. I really dislike this quality in myself, yet somehow I'm unfortunately almost always right. I just chalked it up to my childhood, yet it only started there the real pain and heart ache came when I thought I had my family behind and created a new real support system. I CAN NOT believe I forgot this! Back then my friends were my world, I had so many people around me, and we were tight! I Loved them and they Loved me, I gave them my all. Then when the few reacted the way they did about me being gay, it changed me, to what I am now. Also every time I did give someone a little trust, and they ended up hurting me, well add more green to the Jade please. Sorry I'm sure this post is very boring, yet for me it truly is a huge deal.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0793f7d589f1e5ee5bc861a2e97d9b25f26e4980.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/coming-out-day-age-22/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02fa9dc9-6601-4f43-a0f2-5e2554940455</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 20:01:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/af4c8023-c273-42bd-9a6e-b0b42d43ced3.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/this-is-the-very-start-of-that-magical-lavinder/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a59febf4-2c1f-4acc-b528-77aea6b3270b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 06:58:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/099e3ed9-1fa9-4428-90dd-795b5b7478ef.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/its-the-little-big-moments-in-my-life-time-i-have-not/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6f0ec781-8c94-4d63-a5ff-1d891d24e4f2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 06:58:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AGH - Yummy (DJ Sandy Electro Dub)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>AGH - Yummy (DJ Sandy Electro Dub)</h1><p>This is D.J. Sandy, he is so amazing on tables it's like watching magic! We use to have great times at Club Firestone! The Roxy was great too, and oh how the Edge will always hold my heart! So many little BIG GREAT moments!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e1b062e65061698c79875a27e98297e1bd92b04c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/sas_H2yTiVo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d6468ab8-233c-4321-a55a-a8594f9ad24a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 05:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Yet to ask this question, I most surely have lived right?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/035205f1-68f1-4dd1-b3ff-7233a95efb1a.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wood-mizer/6701e543-1066-4e66-b4cd-0fbb82c34ca9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6701e543-1066-4e66-b4cd-0fbb82c34ca9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2016 03:42:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>